<blog>
	<post>
		<date>4/22/89</date>
		<author>Saul Goodman</author>
		<title>Saul Goodman Commits Tax Fraud</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.ibb.co/F3Lhgvq/sual.jpg</image_path>
			<text>"And I'll do it again"</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Saul Goodman has been (allegedly) accussed of committing tax fraud. He was arrested on Monday, July 7, and is currently incarcinated at Oregon private prison. However, other sources claim that the suppossed culprit isn't actually in said prison, but rather a dummy. This is because Saul Goodman is an innocent man, who would never do anything to anyone, and has a burning hatred for the IRS. Who knows if Saul will ever pay his taxes?</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>4/22/22</date>
		<author>Walter White</author>
		<title>George Jetson Close to Being Born</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.ibb.co/31r8G1C/gorj.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Our lord and savior will be with us soon</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Word about a certain man's arrival has been making it's rounds on the internet for the past few days. George Jetson: one of the main characters on the animated show The Jetsons, a father of two, and the husband of Jane Jetson. Fact-checkers claim to have discovered George's birthday: August 22, 2022. This would place the man's birth about four months from now. Of course, this is all simply speculation. There is no definitive proof that George Jetson will be born this coming August, but like with most things, we'll just have to wait and see.</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>4/22/22</date>
		<author>Mike Wazowski</author>
		<title>Mike Tyson Punches Man on Plane</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://i.ibb.co/VLtmsQh/mike.jpg</image_path>
			<text>Looks like his boxing career is taking off again: just like the plane</text>
		</summary>
		<body>Former heavyweight boxing champion 'Iron' Mike Tyson has reportedly punched a guy on an airplane. During the flight, Mikey was minding his own business when the man came from behind his seat and started verbally harrassing him. Mike, having more than enough of his crap, got up and struck the man repeatedly in the side of his head. All of this information comes from camera footage from the friend of the man, who recorded the harrassment and the savage beating. What do you think about the situation? If you want my take: the dude kinda deserved it tbh.</body>
	</post>
</blog>